(Leonard:)I am not going
to have sex with her.
(Sheldon:)Maybe this will overcome
your reluctance.
(Sheldon:)I went on the Internet
and found a photograph
(Sheldon:)of a 25-year-old Mrs. Latham
to get your libido humming.
(Sheldon:)Check out those saddle shoes.
(Leonard:)Are you insane?
(Leonard:)I'm not going
to prostitute myself
(Leonard:)just so we can get
some new equipment.
(Sheldon:)Oh, come on! Why not?
(Leonard:)Good night,
(Howard:)Sheldon.
Given how much time
(Sheldon:)you spend engaging
in pointless self-abuse,
(Sheldon:)you might consider,
just this once,
(Sheldon:)using your genitalia to
actually accomplish something!
(Penny:)He still won't shag
the old lady, huh?
(Sheldon:)No. But thank you for asking.
(Leonard:)Hey. Hi.
(Mrs Latham:)Hello, Leonard.
(Mrs Latham:)I hope you're hungry.
(Leonard:)I'm very hungry.
(Leonard:)For food, right?